// Very WIP -Slinky
"lang"
{ 
	"Language" "English" 
	"Tokens" 
	{ 
		"testcommands"			"<clr:255,0,0>This is red<I> and italics<B> and<cr>bold<B><I><clr:255,255,255> white again."

		// HEV Suit
		"HEV.subzero"					"<sfx><clr:255,170,0>Warning: Atmospheric sensors detecting sub-zero temperatures, shutting down non-vital systems to reserve power.<cr>Increasing H.E.V. internal suit temperature to an acceptible level.<cr>Please seek immediate shelter."

		// Barney
		"Interlude.Dialogue.Barney.MonitorOne"		"<clr:215,255,255><I>Hello? Hello? Is someone there? Look, I don't know who's turning the lights back on but whoever you are, you're walking into a death trap. That facility is not safe, not anymore!"
		"part1.barney_monitor_take1"		"<clr:215,255,255><I>[Signal Incoming] Hello? Hello? Is someone there? Look, I don't know who's turning the lights back on but whoever you are, you're walking into a death trap. That facility is not safe, not anymore!<delay:15><clr:215,255,255><I>Combine came through here like a storm. The lower levels they're flooded structural damage it's a breeding ground for those things you won't seem them until it's too la-[Signal Lost]"

		// Audio Captions
		"Interlude.Object.Ignite"			"<sfx><norepeat:4>[Object Ignites]"
		"Interlude.Object.Extinguish"			"<sfx><norepeat:4>[Object Extinguished]"

		// Audio Logs
		"part1.audiolog_1"		"[Coughing] I-I've been shot. The damn combine must've found out what we were doing here and caught us by surprise.<delay:20>We were so close to [Coughing] I got seperated from Mossman and the others I [Coughing]<delay:30>Don't know if they managed to escape. If anyone finds this message your best shot at finding Mossman's team is reactivating the radio tower.<delay:40>If she's still out there that'll get her attention. The radio tower's in the big dome up ahead you can't miss it.<len:20><delay:48>Whoever you are goodluck! Not even sure Gordon Freeman can pull this one off. Oh no! [Headcrab noise]<len:15>"
		"part1.audiolog_2"		"We've been stationed out here for [Skip]<delay:5>Still no sign of that ship. It's always on the move and we cannot keep up with it. All we have is loose containers and Aperture scrap and yet Mossman seems fixated on something else.<delay:20>Despite her best efforts I've seen her notes and god help us if I'm right but those signals she's decoding it's somehow Breen.<len:18><delay:30>I fear if she continues with her efforts it could lead the combine right to us.<len:10>"
		"part1.audiolog_3"		"Headcrabs. How do they even survive out here? These temperatures should freeze them solid but they're not just surviving they're adapting. Some of the others say they're taller than me and they're not just big they're smart too. It's not just them the anomalies in this area. They're changing the wildlife making it more suited to these conditions harder to kill. It's like this whole place is evolving to fight back against us. Rumors are they've been seen in the lower levels where the base is flooded. Just the thought of it those things crawling beneath us in the dark waiting. If it's true I don't think I'll sleep again [Metal Clank] I hate this base."

		// Vort
		"part1.vort_interlude3"		"Aha the one Freeman...<delay:5>The strains of our fate converge once more our meeting place lays not far beyond.<len:12>"

		//Gman
		"intro.gman_int_2"		"What was it you were expecting to find here Mr. Freeman rescue undoing? Or perhaps [breath in] something else."
		"intro.gman_int_3"		"Time as you know waits for no man. Each second a wave each minute a tide."
		"intro.gman_int_4"		"Before time runs out."
		"intro.gman_int_5"		"It's time to cross these empty shores these white sands."
		
	}
}